Minecraft中的物品经历过多次更名
Minecraft items have been renamed many times.
翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
末地水晶曾被称为末影水晶
End Crystals were called Ender Crystals,
劫掠兽曾被称为灾厄兽
Ravagers were called Illager Beasts,
使用AI工具翻译，如有不准确的地方请在弹幕或评论区指正，谢谢！
！！真的有人看不到这行字！！
而深板岩曾被称为幽冥石？
and Deepslate was called Grimstone?
今天我将为大家盘点25个在Minecraft中被重命名的物品
So today, I bring you 25 items that were renamed in Minecraft.
回溯Minecraft早期版本
Back in the earlier days of Minecraft,
翻译质量权威评价：原来25年就有小拉即用机翻糊弄人了
游戏中原本只有两种花卉
there used to be only two flowers in the game,
分别是玫瑰与黄色花朵
which was the rose and the yellow flower.
在很长一段时间里
Now, for the longest time,
黄色花朵仅被称作“花”
the yellow flower was just called Flower,
注意：本视频译名不遵循我的世界标准译名，请自行查询！
但随着1.7版本更新加入了其他花卉
but when all the other flowers were added in the 1.7 update,
它被更名为蒲公英
the flower was renamed to the dandelion.
蒲公英这个名称显然比单纯的“花”更具辨识度
A dandelion definitely sounds a lot more descriptive than just a flower.
干草捆
The hay bale.
众所周知这是个实用方块
We all know it's a useful block,
能分解出大量小麦
as you can get a bunch of wheat from it,
用来制作成堆面包
which allows you to make a bunch of bread.
干草捆在1.6版本加入游戏
The hay bale was added in the 1.6 update,
但你们知道它最初并非此名吗？
but did you know it wasn't always called this?
没错 在1.6版本的早期快照阶段
That's right, during the early snapshot phase for 1.6,
干草捆最初被称为干草块
the hay bale was originally called the hay block,
但在后续的1.6版本快照中
but then in a later snapshot for 1.6,
干草块被更名为干草捆
the hay block was renamed to the hay bale,
并沿用至今
and that's how it's been ever since.
Minecraft 中有众多铜质方块可选
In Minecraft, there are loads of different copper-related blocks to choose from,
但最值得关注的是铜块
but the one copper block to pay attention to is the block of copper,
原因如下
and here is why.
当铜块在1.17洞穴与山崖更新中加入时
So when the block of copper was added in the 1.17 caves and cliffs update,
快照版本中原本命名为“铜块”
it was originally called the copper block in the snapshot,
但在后续1.17快照中
but then in a later snapshot for the 1.17 update,
这个方块从“铜块”
the copper block was renamed from being called the,
更名为“铜质方块”
well, copper block, to the block of copper.
我知道 这简直是游戏史上最有趣的改动
I know, I know, that was the most interesting change in Minecraft history.
言归正传
Anyways, moving on.
在Java版中
In Minecraft Java Edition,
熟猪肉被称为“熟猪排”
a pork chop when it's simply called cooked pork chop.
而在基岩版中
But in Minecraft Bedrock Edition,
不知何故被命名为“熟牛肉”
the cooked pork chop for whatever reason was renamed to say cooked beef.
为何同一食物在两个平台会有不同名称
Why this food item has a different name between the two platforms,
至今无人知晓
I'll never know.
众所周知游戏中有西瓜籽
So we all know in Minecraft we have the melon seeds,
西瓜片和西瓜块
the melon slice, and the melon block.
但你们是否知道长久以来
But did you know for the longest time,
西瓜片与西瓜块都统称为“西瓜”
both the melon slice and the melon block were both just simply called melon.
直到1.13海洋更新
But then in the 1.13 aquatic update,
可食用的部分才从“西瓜”
the melon that you can eat was renamed from being called melon,
更名为“西瓜片”
to the melon slice.
龟壳可用于制作海龟帽
So we all know the turtle scute is used to craft a turtle shell,
佩戴后能延长水下呼吸时间
which can be worn by the player and allows them to breathe underwater for longer.
但你们知道它最初并非此名吗？
However, did you know the turtle scute wasn't always called this?
当龟壳最初出现在1.13快照版时
That's right, when the turtle scute was first added in the 1.13 snapshot,
它原本被命名为“龟壳碎片”
it was originally called the turtle shell piece.
但在后续的1.13快照中
But then in a later snapshot for 1.13,
又从“龟壳碎片”更名为“鳞甲”
it was renamed from a turtle shell piece to simply be called a scute.
故事并未结束
But it doesn't end there,
在1.20.5版本更新中
as in the 1.20.5 update,
它再次被更名为“海龟鳞甲”
the scute was renamed to be called the turtle scute,
并沿用至今
and that's what it's been called ever since.
刷怪笼早在2010年的infdev阶段就已加入游戏
The monster spawner was added into Minecraft in the infdev phase all the way back in 2010.
它们与地牢同时问世
They were added alongside dungeons,
当时地牢是游戏中唯一的建筑结构
which were the only structure in Minecraft at the time.
在旧版本中获取刷怪笼的唯一方式是通过指令
Now the only way to obtain the monster spawner in old versions of Minecraft was by using commands,
这个方块当时的物品名称是“怪物刷怪笼”
and as you can see, the item name for the block at the time was monster spawner.
但不知出于何种原因
But then, for whatever reason,
在1.13海洋更新中
in the 1.13 aquatic update,
它被简化为“刷怪笼”
the monster spawner was renamed to simply say spawner.
而后在1.19.3的某个快照中
But then in a random snapshot for 1.19.3,
又改回了“怪物刷怪笼”
the spawner was renamed back to monster spawner.
或许是觉得“刷怪笼”这个名称过于单调
I guess the name spawner was a bit too boring,
所以恢复了原来的叫法
so they changed it back.
各位观众 接下来这个物品重命名堪称重磅
Okay guys, this next item rename is a huge one,
因为大箱子在1.3正式版中被更名为“大箱子”
because the large chest was renamed to the large chest in release 1.3.
没错 在1.3版本中
That's right, in 1.3,
大箱子界面标题的首字母改成了大写
the large chest inventory title was changed to capital C,
这可谓是我的世界划时代的改动
which is a massive change from Minecraft,
劫掠兽是在1.14村庄与掠夺更新中加入的
The ravager was added in the 1.14 village and pillage update.
这种凶残生物确实能让你吃尽苦头
Now the ravager is indeed a very scary mob that can mess you up pretty bad,
但可知它最初并非叫这个名字？
but did you know it wasn't always called the ravager?
没错 在1.14村庄与掠夺更新的快照阶段
That's right, during the snapshot phase for the 1.14 village and pillage update,
劫掠兽最初被命名为“灾厄兽”
the ravager was originally called the illager beast.
由于这个命名渊源
Since the ravager was originally called the illager beast,
其刷怪蛋也沿用了这个名称
the spawn egg for the mob was also called this.
但在后续的1.14快照中
But then in a later snapshot for 1.14,
“灾厄兽”被正式更名为“劫掠兽”
the illager beast was officially renamed to the ravager,
相应的刷怪蛋也随之改名
which meant the spawn egg was renamed as well.
砂岩早在2011年的Beta1.2版本就已加入游戏
Sandstone was added into Minecraft in beta 1.2 in 2011,
但砂岩变体直到2012年的1.2正式版才问世
but we didn't get the sandstone variant until release 1.2 in 2012.
有趣的是在1.2正式版时期
What's interesting is during release 1.2,
砂岩及其所有变体都共用“砂岩”这个统一名称
sandstone along with its variants did not have unique item names and instead all shared the name sandstone.
直到1.3正式版更新时 所有砂岩变体才获得了专属的物品名称
It wasn't until release 1.3 where all the sandstone variants were given their own unique item names.
尽管砂岩变体在1.3版本已拥有独立名称
Now despite the sandstone variants receiving their own names in version 1.3,
但平滑砂岩在1.13海洋更新中被更名为“切制砂岩"”
the smooth sandstone block was eventually renamed to cut sandstone in the 1.13 aquatic update.
这很可能是因为在1.5正式版中新增了另一种平滑砂岩——当你在熔炉中
This was likely done as another smooth sandstone block was added in release 1.5 where if you smelted sandstone in a
烧炼普通砂岩时 会获得另一种名为“平滑砂岩”的方块
furnace, you would get another block called smooth sandstone.
确实 如果存在两种都叫“平滑砂岩”的方块 势必会造成混淆
So yeah, it definitely would have been very confusing if there were two sandstone blocks called smooth sandstone.
不仅平滑砂岩在1.13版本更名
Not only was smooth sandstone renamed to cut sandstone in 1.13,
红色砂岩变体也经历了改名
the red variant of the sandstone block was also renamed.
没错 在海洋更新中
That's right, in the aquatic update,
平滑红色砂岩被重新命名为“切制红色砂岩”
the smooth red sandstone was renamed to cut red sandstone.
深板岩是一种生成于主世界深层地下的岩石类型 其功能与普通岩石相似
Deepslate is a stone type found deep underground in the overworld and it functions similar to regular stone but it takes
但挖掘耗时显著更长
significantly longer to break.
深板岩虽在1.17洞穴与山崖更新中加入 但可知它并非始终叫这个名字？
Now deepslate was added in the 1.17 caves and cliffs update but did you know it wasn't always called deepslate?
事实上 在1.17更新的早期快照阶段
That's right, during the early snapshot phase for the 1.17 update,
该方块原本被命名为“幽冥岩”
the deepslate block was originally called grimstone.
而在后续的1.17快照中
But then in a later snapshot for 1.17,
不仅深板岩的纹理与模型被调整 其名称也从“幽冥岩”变更为“深板岩”
the texture and model of deepslate was changed as well as being renamed from grimstone to deepslate.
据开发者Brandon Pearce解释
Now according to Minecraft developer Brandon Pearce,
更名原因是“幽冥”一词蕴含过多负面情感联想
the reason for changing the name grimstone to deepslate was because the word grim had too many connotations related to a negative feeling.
他还说明最终选定“深板岩”这个名称既体现了其在地下深处的生成位置
He also stated that the name deepslate was eventually chosen because of its location within the world and it more
又更准确地表明这是一种板岩材质
accurately represented that it is a type of slate.
我欣赏开发团队坦言“幽冥岩”听起来更酷的说法
I like that they also stated that grimstone sounded cooler because I do agree,
就方块名称而言 我也认为幽冥岩确实比深板岩更显酷炫 但深板岩确实更能准确体现该方块特性
I think grimstone does sound cooler than deepslate as block names go but deepslate definitely represents the block a lot better.
小麦种子
Wheat seeds.
我们都使用过它们 播种 等待生长 最终制成面包
We've all used them, you plant them and then they grow and then you make some bread with it.
但是否知道在1.13海洋更新之前 小麦种子始终被简称为“种子”？
But did you know that the wheat seeds before the 1.13 aquatic update were just called seeds?
没错 这个冷知识确实很有趣
Yeah I know, that's really interesting isn't it?
在某个1.13快照中 种子被正式更名为小麦种子 整段历史大致如此
But uh yeah, in a random snapshot for 1.13 the seeds were renamed to wheat seeds and uh yeah that's uh pretty much it.
话说回来 在荒野更新中青蛙与蝌蚪 青蛙卵同步加入游戏
Anyways moving on, frogs along with tadpoles and frogspawn were added in the wild update.
但是否知道基岩版荒野更新测试阶段 青蛙卵曾使用过不同名称？
But did you know in the experiment phase for the wild update in bedrock edition frogspawn actually had a different name?
没错 当时不叫“青蛙卵”而称作“蛙蛋”
That's right, instead of being called frogspawn it was instead called frog egg.
不过在后续测试版本中 “蛙蛋”被更名为“青蛙卵”
But then in a later experiment test build the frog egg was renamed to frogspawn.
故事尚未结束——就在基岩版荒野更新即将发布时
But it doesn't end there because right as the wild update was going to be released for bedrock edition the frogspawn was
原本由两个单词组成的“青蛙卵”又被合并成了单个单词
renamed once again to just be one word as it was two words before.
胡萝卜早在2012年的1.4版本就已加入游戏 请注意我使用的是复数形式
Carrots were added in the Minecraft 1.4 update all the way back in 2012 and yes I did say carrots plural as the old
因为旧版纹理呈现的是一捆胡萝卜而非单根
texture used to be a bunch of instead of just a single carrot.
这也体现在物品名称上——当使用该纹理时物品栏显示的是复数而非单数形式
This also reflected in its item name as when the carrots had this texture it was called carrots in the inventory instead of carrot.
随后在1.4的更新中 胡萝卜纹理改为单根 物品名称也从复数改为单数形式
But then in a later update for 1.4 the carrot texture was changed to be a single carrot and the item was renamed from carrots to carrot.
天啊 我刚才到底说了多少次胡萝卜？
Oh my god how many times did I say carrot just then?
话说回来 灵魂火把作为蓝色火把变种 是在1.16下界更新中加入的
Anyways moving on, the soul torch is a blue torch variant that was added in the 1.16 nether update.
但你是否知道 在1.16下界更新的快照阶段被叫做“灵魂火火把”
But did you know during the snapshot phase for the 1.16 nether update the soul torch was instead called the soul fire torch.
这个名称并未沿用太久 在后续的1.16快照中“灵魂火火把”就更名为灵魂火把
This didn't last too long as in a later snapshot for 1.16 the soul fire torch was renamed to the soul torch.
同样的情况也发生在灵魂灯笼上——在1.16版本快照阶段 它原本被称为灵魂火灯笼
The same also applies to the soul lantern as during the snapshot phase for the 1.16 update it was instead called the soul fire lantern.
棕色蘑菇和红色蘑菇几乎从创世之初就存在于我的世界中
The brown mushroom and the red mushroom have been in Minecraft since pretty much the beginning of time as they were
早在2009年的classic版本阶段就已加入游戏
added all the way back in the classic phase in 2009.
长久以来 棕色蘑菇和红色蘑菇在物品栏中都只被统称为“蘑菇”
Now for the longest time both the brown and red mushroom were just called mushroom in the inventory.
随后在1.13海洋更新中 蘑菇的名称被改为棕色蘑菇与红色蘑菇
But then in the 1.13 aquatic update the names of the mushrooms were changed to be called the brown mushroom and the red mushroom respectively.
众所周知 在如今的我的世界中 黏土球与黏土块各有其名
So we all know in Minecraft today the clay ball and the clay block have their own different names.
黏土球曾叫做
The clay ball is called,
黏土球 与黏土块都统称为黏土
well, clay ball and the clay block is simply called clay.
但在1.16下界更新前的早期版本中 这两种方块都统称为黏土
But back in the earlier days of Minecraft before the 1.16 nether update both of these blocks were simply called clay.
2013年的1.7版本更新中新增了一种可用钓竿捕获的鱼类
In the 1.7 update in 2013 Minecraft added a new fish type that you could catch with a fishing rod and this new fish was
小丑鱼
the clownfish.
这些年来小丑鱼基本保持不变 直到1.13海洋更新才发生改变 事情是这样的
Now the clownfish remained mostly unchanged over the years but this all changed in the 1.13 aquatic update and here is why.
1.13海洋更新加入了多种在水中游弋的新鱼类 其中你能找到的一种鱼就是热带鱼
So the 1.13 aquatic update added a bunch of new fish to swim around in the water and one of the fish types you can find are tropical fish.
众所周知 当你击杀热带鱼生物时 它们会掉落作为物品的热带鱼
Now as you know when you kill a tropical fish mob it will drop a tropical fish as an item.
但你是否知道 这个热带鱼物品最初是小丑鱼 因为在1.13的快照阶段 这种鱼
But did you know this tropical fish item was originally the clownfish as in the snapshot phase for 1.13 this fish was
从“小丑鱼”更名为“热带鱼”
renamed from clownfish to tropical fish.
说真的 每次看到这个热带鱼纹理 我总会想起《海底总动员》里的小丑鱼马林
I mean I'll be real whenever I look at this tropical fish texture I just think of Marlin the clownfish from Finding Nemo.
末影水晶是矗立于黑曜石柱顶端的实体
End crystals are entities that are found on top of obsidian pillars.
摧毁末影水晶能帮助你击败末影龙
Destroying them helps you defeat the ender dragon.
末影水晶也能被合成物品形态 让玩家能够重新召唤末影龙
End crystals can also be crafted into item form that allows the player to respawn the dragon as well.
早在2011年的beta1.9版本中加入时 这些实体原本被称为“末地水晶”
When end crystals were added all the way back in beta 1.9 in 2011 they were instead called ender crystals.
这个名称一直沿用到1.9战斗更新版本 才最终更名为
These entities were called ender crystals all the way up to the 1.9 combat update where they were finally renamed to the
“末影水晶”并沿用至今
end crystals and that's how they've been ever since.
我的世界中还有更多物品经历过重命名
There are many more items that were renamed in Minecraft,
如果你们想看第二部分请告诉我
let me know if you want to see a part 2.
那么下次见！
Anyways bye!